#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/datnguyen0207 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Master CopyCat Nuke
Al Engineer
Prompt Design

# Nguyen Dat

Al Researcher, Compositor, Diffusion Model, Stable Diffusion, GAN, Deep Fake, Generative Al, LLMs

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

## Summary

Using AI to assist companies in addressing challenges in the VFX pipeline: optimizing workflows, solving image-related issues, and enhancing final rendering outputs for projects.

Research on AI models and papers to improve traditional VFX workflows

## Experience

AIOI Studios AI Researcher March 2022 - Present (3 years 1 month) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

BadClay Studio Ltd Compositor July 2019 - March 2022 (2 years 9 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Compositor at BadClay Studio

Magnon studio Compositor January 2018 - December 2018 (1 year) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Take over the compositor position

#### Education

VTC Academy
Al SPECIALIST - Al ENGINEER · (December 2021 - September 2022)

APTECH Computer Education
Developer · (2011 - 2013)